What's wrong?
Did you bite your tongue?
It's my tooth...
It's wobbly...
Don't touch it!
What should I do?
You have another one coming in under it, so just leave it alone.
Do you want your rice as porridge?
No, it'll be fine if I eat slowly.
Bunny Drop
I dunno about tomorrow
It's different than a sacrifice Something's off
I don't think it's like some penalty game
So, why? I don't get it at all
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
Cultural Festival
Daikichi!
Hey.
W-Why the rush?
Look, there's my drawing!
Kaga Rin
Your dad always comes to these things, huh Rin?
Yeah.
Although he's not my dad...
He's not?!
Hey, it's pretty good.
Say, did you know?
Rin's the best artist in Class B!
You don't say...
I bet you could become a comic artist!
No way!
I'm sure you could!
Papa!
Over here!
Sorry I'm late.
This stylish guy is her dad?!
How handsome!
Lucky!
He's so tall!
Guess what! Sayaka's dad is 31, just like you, Daikichi!
Seriously?!
Really? What a happy coincidence.
My papa's a model!
Wow!
Come on now, Sayaka!
Just a little.
When I was younger...
I think I might've seen you in my company's catalog before...
Really?!
Hold on...
Might I ask the name of your company?
That really might be me!
I'm so flattered!
Cheerful guy, isn't he?
How embarrassing!
I'm just a manager for my agency these days.
Oh, really?
It seems like kind of a waste...
You don't have a steady income or hours when you model,
so when my daughter was born, I called it a day.
Oh...
While I spent every night drinking and bitching about work...
Hey, Mi!
Nabe! Long time no see!
We were classmates.
We're from the same neighborhood.
He's got a boy in Class A.
This is Rin's father, Daikichi.
He's the same age as us.
Oh yeah? Nice to meet you!
Likewise.
These two are the type that protect their kids...
Daikichi!
I'm a butcher.
My shop's on the corner of that shopping street.
Rin and I often get take-out croquettes there.
Really? I'm so happy!
Me too! I do too!
Well I know that!
I made some papa-pals...
In a sense, the world may be wider here...
Hey there.
Hello!
It got cold pretty fast, huh?
Yeah.
It seems the kids are already in the gym.
I just hope he has his jacket on...
Yeah...
Nitani Kouki
Wow, he's quite the artist.
Really?
I mean, you can tell he put a lot of time into it...
You know, everybody else is in the gym already.
Seriously?!
Crap! My teacher's gonna be mad!
Boys will be boys...
Oh, how adorable! How many months?
Almost 10 months now.
I love babies!
How nostalgic...
So my kid had the flu last week...
I'm sorry I've kept you...
Oh, really? That must've been rough.
Not at all!
Is it that season already?
They have to stay home for two days even if the fever's down, right?
So it doesn't spread...
Yeah, but I sent him to school right after his temperature went down.
Well, what else could you do?
You don't wanna be fired either.
Right, and he was getting better, so the virus was probably weak anyway.
Oh, I'm sure...
Besides, even if he did pass it on, nobody would ever know who did it.
Shall we depart?
Um... What those mothers were talking about kind of hit home...
And that makes me even more depressed...
I can relate with the work situation...
Yeah, I know...
When it gets cold out, I become a nervous wreck.
With Kouki the way he is...
Put your pajamas on now!
But once winter ends and it starts getting warm, I can relax.
Daikichi!
Daikichi, wait while I go grab my bag!
Are you two kidding me?!
Kouki, your nose!
I told you to wear your jacket because it's cold in the gym!
And don't run in the halls!
Okay!
Don't run, hear me?!
Kouki's baby teeth are already starting to come out, huh?
We live in an apartment complex, so we can't really toss them onto the roof.
And he hasn't been listening to me at all lately.
Well, I can't really talk...
I used to wear the absolute minimum...
And run down the stairs full speed, skipping every other step...
I'd wolf down lunch, drink the milk in one gulp...
It feels really weird telling kids not to do everything that I did.
You did all that, Daikichi?
I think it's normal for a boy...
Anyway, I don't think of Kouki as just another kid.
S-Sorry...
But if you were like that too, Daikichi,
then I'm a little more relieved.
What's wrong? Walk with Kouki!
I don't wanna!
Then let's split into the boys' team and girls' team!
Isn't Rin's face a bit flushed?
I think she's got a fever.
It might get higher.
Way more flushed than normal!
Well, it's not the flu.
For now, please have all of the family members wear a mask.
Okay.
That's good news, huh?
Yeah!
Huh?
Are you done?
Yeah... It feels kinda weird here...
The doctor said it was the stomach flu, so you don't have to force yourself.
Yeah... I feel kind of...
Rin!
W-Washbowl!
A
103.64°F
Rin does?!
Call an ambulance right away!
No, I already had her checked out by a doctor and we got medicine,
but she won't take it!
Her fever keeps climbing higher and she looks like she's suffering...
I bet you had her wear light clothes!
That's not important!
Did you try mixing the medicine in with juice?
You always drank it right away if it was mixed with something sweet.
I'll try it.
Thanks, Mom.
Here, just try a little.
It's sweet.
Come on, just a spoonful.
Daikichi...
I'm sorry for coming so early.
How's Rin doing?
Ah, hold on!
May I come in?
Daikichi, what's with that hair?
Sure...
She doesn't have the flu, but...
Kouki, go watch TV over there.
Yay!
Quietly!
She just managed to fall asleep.
Her fever keeps rising...
And it seems like she can't really sleep.
She's not sweating at all...
Can she take fluids?
I was told to at least give her sports drinks,
but she won't eat or drink anything.
I don't know what to do...
W-What?!
You can't get worried!
The adult has to stay calm and tell her it's going to be all right...
It's hard.
I've never seen Rin like that before.
It's not hard! You can do it!
When a child is in real trouble,
an adult who can help needs to be by their side.
Rin will be fine as long as you're there, Daikichi.
Rin...
You're Kouki's mom...
You must be thirsty.
Wanna try sucking on some ice?
How's that?
It feels good...
Rin! You're up?!
I'm sorry, I was in the bathroom...
Daikichi!
Sorry.
You can have some more ice in a little bit, okay?
If you eat it all at once, you'll upset your tummy...
Okay.
I just put something sweet and yummy in the fridge for later.
I'm sorry. You'll be late for work, won't you?
Rin's really doing her best.
If you're here for her, she'll be okay, Daikichi.
Right. Thank you...
You too, Kouki. Thanks.
Sure.
Sorry. I might have to take off tomorrow too.
If something comes up, give me a call.
Gotcha.
Sorry for the trouble...
What are you talkin' about?!
Please, leave everything to me!
Thank you...
Can you eat a little bit?
Yeah...
When you have a cold, you get to eat all these sweets.
Later.
You'll get better after a bit more rest.
Why'd it have to be Rin?
If I'd gotten it, it'd be nothing.
Damn it!
Damn it! God damn it!
Yeah?
Daikichi!
Hey!
Kouki!
How do you feel, Rin?
Does it hurt anywhere?
I'm okay.
I'm going to make you some yummy rice porridge now, okay?
Her fever's been up again since this afternoon...
It's all right.
It's normal for people's body temperature to rise as the day goes on.
But... it was over 102 degrees earlier.
Here, put this in the pot.
Sure.
Daikichi...
Water...
That looks good...
I made it for you too, Daikichi.
Daikichi! Rin wants water!
Got it!
Kouki, I don't want you catching it, so stay here, okay?
I don't mind getting it.
Don't say that!
But thanks...
Kouki, thank you.
Kouki, when you're here, Rin feels totally at ease.
Yeah...
Here, Rin, eat a little bit.
Don't worry. When Kouki gets sick, he eats this too.
It's special porridge that makes you get better fast.
Kouki too?
That's right...
When he eats this, his cold just disappears!
It's good!
Daikichi!
Rin! Are you better?
Yeah.
I feel fine.
I'm hungry!
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
Can you give your mom my thanks for the other night?
She looked after Rin, so...
Hey, can I go home with you guys?
Again?!
Your mom has to be the one who picks you up from here!
But my mom's in bed with a cold.
What?! Are you serious?!